Come on.
Hang in there.
You'll be fine.
Boss Wan will be here soon.
Swamp Eel.
If I die,
you have to take care of my wife
and Chia-yun. All right?
Take care, my ass.
You're the one
who's gonna take care of them. All right?
Fuck, who am I?
I'm Swamp Eel.
I shot flies to get where I am.
You're in good hands.
You're gonna be all right.
Relax, relax.
Hang in there. You're gonna be fine.
Hang in there, will you?
-Quick, quick, in there!
-Fuck.
-We can get down…
-They'll be here.
Get out.
Wan's not coming.
They'll be here. Don't you worry.
They'll be here.
You're lying to yourself.
If they were coming,
they'd be here already.
And you know that.
Hang in there.
Don't worry.
You're in good hands.
You're gonna be all right.
Hang in there. You're gonna be fine.
Hang in there, will you? Fuck you!
Hang in there.
I get to fire the shot.
The one I didn't get to fire back then.
You still hung up about A-chi?
While I still have breath,
I will never forget.
Lin Wan-li, you were never worthy
of being a leader.
After I leave the mountain,
it'll be my own brother who sees me off.
I would rather die by your hand.
Go on and shoot.
You bastard.
You told us to ambush those traitors.
You said you'd send reinforcements,
but what happened?
A-chi's death.
It's on your head.
They were so prepared,
and they had powerful backers.
If I had sent anyone,
the death count would have been higher.
If I had a second chance,
my decision would remain unchanged.
-Swamp Eel.
-Yeah?
Tell Boss Wan
I'm leaving now.
Tell him to take care.
Did you know?
As A-chi died…
he still called you the leader.
Don't forget.
You're still living
thanks to him.
If you can wake up, that's a good sign.
THE FIXERS
ONE SHORT
Nothing to worry about, sweetie.
It's just my ear got a little hurt.
It'll be all right.
A-pin and A-hsiu, those clowns.
They've almost managed to split San He.
I'll see you after I've sorted things.
Uh-huh. Take care.
Hsiu, our people saw with their own eyes
you were the kidnappers.
You got the ransom money.
If anything happens to my brother,
I'll make you pay for it.
There's also the chance
you're the kidnapper.
What did he say?
Enough!
What's going on?
Get out of the way. Move back.
-Boss.
Boss.
Is this a stare-down?
Move back!
A-pin.
Thank goodness
you had people looking for me everywhere.
However, I was abducted by two idiots
who had nothing to do with A-hsiu.
And what did I say before?
Peace above all.
This incident was all a misunderstanding.
It would be respectful
if you were to let this matter rest.
As members of San He,
we have to look after each other
so that others don't take advantage.
Since everyone's here,
I'd like to take this chance
to make an announcement.
This dear young brother of mine
has coveted my position for a long time.
But during my life,
I've let down too many people
who have called me brother.
Hmm.
It's time to step down.
And you're sure
that your brother's the right candidate.
Mm.
As of today, all association affairs
are to be handed over
to my brother, Lin Kuei-pin.
-It's about time.
-I am retiring.
You have to be ruthless in your actions.
When you need to, betray your family.
Like this time, A-pin.
You wanted to take your own brother out.
Which just proves you're more ruthless.
San He.
It's all yours.
Okay?
As for Fixer Shadow,
Hsiu's helped us take care of it.
For people like us,
shouldering the blame for others
isn't an issue, is it?
You're an important client of Ching He.
If it's you who spreads the word, then…
then all should be fine.
Who would dare
threaten Ching He's people, huh?
Hey, you need some swamp eel.
It's good for the blood and builds muscle.
And good for healing.
Wow!
Light rain on the streets, soft as milk.
It's like a display home, isn't it?
-Fortune.
-Yeah.
Sit. Say hello to our guest.
The dog is also called Fortune.
Is that deliberate?
What do you think?
How are you? The wound getting better?
Ah, I'll survive.
Let me tell you,
you're fortunate to have met me.
If anyone else had treated that wound,
you'd be crippled. Ha.
When I was young, I was shot three times.
Shoulder, abdomen, and left thigh.
There were two words to describe it.
Close shave. Ha.
Are you going to ask what happened?
Why should I?
You got better.
Yeah. If you're gonna give me nothing,
I might as well talk to my buddy, Fortune.
Fortune, come here.
Good dog.
Ha.
Ah.
That guy looks familiar.
Is that the person
who's running for mayor?
The one who's always on the news.
How come you two are in a photo together?
-Why so many questions?
-Wait.
-You two are looking quite similar.
-He's my brother.
The older one.
Your older brother.
Holy shit.
Hey, why is someone like you
working as a fixer?
Are you mad?
It makes me happy. Eat, will you?
I respect that. Point taken.
Everybody's got things
they don't wanna talk about.
You look like
you should be the older brother.
-Can I ask you?
-Yeah.
Why'd you spare Lin Wan-li that day?
BELOVED FATHER, CHEN LIANG-CHI
BELOVED MOTHER, WANG SHU-HUA
Mom. Dad.
I got into an American school.
So for a while,
I might not be able to come.
Mm.
A-chi, lowly parents
can produce an exceptional child.
Your Chen Chia-yun, she's amazing.
She's off to the US to study.
And, please, be happy she's flying away.
Give her your blessing
so she's safe and sound.
And hopefully, she'll return
with a foreign boyfriend on her arm.
Sh!
Okay.
Mom, I'm doing great right now.
My brother is looking after me.
Don't worry.
We're playing tennis again.
Though I can still beat him.
And Dad…
Dad's been tied up with work.
He can't make it here,
but don't take it personally.
I wish you were still here.
DAD
From when my great-grandfather
served as a legislator
to now with my father,
my family have dedicated their lives
to serving society.
And now I take the baton.
I will live up to their efforts,
and continue to serve.
Today, I'd like to thank my mother.
She has always stood
by our family's choices.
Without her contribution,
the Hsueh family wouldn't be here.
So are we on a…
a date, or, um…
I think you owe me a favor.
-And why is that?
-You owe your life to me.
I wanted Lin Wan-li to tell me
about someone I need to find.
Is this to do with the necklace?
Yes.
Why are you looking for them?
His name is Gerald Chen.
He's very important to me.
He was a fixer for Yeh Yueh Tong
a long time ago.
Over a year ago, he suddenly vanished.
Lin Wan-li said
that Gerald had come to see him.
Gerald Chen did come for a visit.
It was about someone from Yuan Tao
called Zoe.
But I refused.
I wanted nothing to do with Yeh Yueh Tong.
One of the founders of the Yuan Tao, Zoe,
she died over a year ago
in an accident in Vietnam.
I lost contact with Gerald
around then too.
If I can get into Yuan Tao,
maybe I can find him.
I made contact with Zoe's older sister,
and I'm gonna meet her here.
Oh. Pretending you're her friend.
I went to college with her.
I wasn't aware of the awful news.
We studied abroad together.
I was hoping to catch up.
What about her partner? Is he doing okay?
Her husband's no longer with us.
My sister's family were always cheerful.
I would never have thought that…
Zoe's husband was a legislative aide.
Just before her accident,
he committed suicide.
Does her sister know Gerald Chen?
Mm-mm.
But she did mention
Yuan Tao's other founder.
William.
We also believe
the value of blockchain technology…
William and my sister had a falling out.
I don't wanna cast suspicion on anyone,
but I heard them arguing over Yuan Tao.
Zoe said that William had ruined
the years of effort
she had put into building it.
So you think Zoe's death is related?
He must have known about Zoe.
So he could also have some news
about Gerald.
I need you to help me.
Why don't you ask Yeh Yueh Tong
to help you?
Your family is so well known.
For you to get close
to one of the group's founders
should be a lot easier.
How did you know?
You're not very good at hiding it.
Apart from Fixer Fortune,
I saw you have another friend
from Yeh Yueh Tong.
We're not close,
but she did help out
on the Lin Wan-li case.
I'm not going to pursue it.
If I intended to,
I wouldn't have waited until now.
Did you get your necklace back?
I did.
I'm hearing that you've become close
to a fixer from Ching He.
I wanted my necklace returned.
I didn't reveal anything
about Ching He to her.
Having one more friend in Yeh Yueh Tong
isn't such a bad thing.
Of all the fixers, I trust you the most.
There are certain things
you should know about.
Some years ago, Fixer Lunar,
now Madam Fan of Yeh Yueh Tong,
she and her father
disobeyed Ching He's rules.
As a result,
all the branches elected me
as Fixer Celestial.
Since then,
Madam Fan has harbored a grudge.
Take care.
Soon, Ching He will be less peaceful.
Hence, I'm concerned
there will be trouble ahead.
You need to take more care.
Don't get dragged into it.
If Yeh Yueh Tong does anything
to harm Ching He, I will tell you.
This time San He's commission
didn't go to Yeh Yueh Tong.
How did Madam Fan find out?
It's not about them.
Mina wanted Lin Wan-li
to tell her about someone.
Who is it?
Gerald Chen from Yeh Yueh Tong.
Every time I see you,
I am reminded of Gerald.
If he hadn't gone missing back then,
you two would be
Yeh Yueh Tong's most outstanding fixers.
I wanna find him even more than you do.
Are you sure it's Mina Shen
who wants to find Gerald Chen
and not Yeh Yueh Tong?
I'm sure.
Madam Fan.
Yuan Tao.
Have they ever given us a commission?
Yuan Tao never commissioned Yeh Yueh Tong.
-Is there anything else?
-No.
CHRONIC GI DISCOMFORT?
BEWARE OF PARKINSON'S!
WESTERN MEDICINE:
PARKINSON'S MAY START IN THE GUT
GOLDIE
How long have you had a second cell?
-And who's this young Gold?
-They're a client.
-Male or female?
-Male!
Huh. Don't tell me
you do have another woman.
What other woman?
-This is a phone I use for work.
-Then who's this young Gold?
I'll tell you who the woman is
when I get back.
-Uh, hey!
-I mean, who Gold is.
If you'd stop going on
about this other woman.
If you can't explain it clearly,
how can I let it go?
Felix Chiang, we're still talking here!
STIR-FRIED SWAMP EEL, SWAMP EEL NOODLES
-I wanted to ask.
-You go first.
Or I'll go.
Have you ever heard of…
Parsinkin's disease?
Parkinson's.
-Yes, Parsonnkins.
-Parkin.
All right, whatever.
Anyway…
The doctor says I have it.
Hey, what is it with you?
I say things. You don't reply.
Not replying is fine, but at least eat.
Do what they say,
and don't think about the future.
I could slow you down.
I noticed your hand ages ago.
I know some good specialists.
I could introduce you to one.
I was wondering if you might want to…
work with another fixer.
I'm not doing that.
No other fixer would do it.
Hey. Your turn. What do you want to ask?
-Mina.
-Mm.
She got information from Lin Wan-li
to find someone.
I want you on it.
I'm fine with that.
I haven't told you who the person is.
Yeah, well, with Lin Wan-li,
we were lucky she helped out.
And you know, she's clearly the one
my partner likes, so how could I not?
I've noticed
that you've got a little crush.
Hey, I know a person
who fixes these things.
They're a fixer of love.
It is I. I'll teach you a few tricks.
Hey. A side hustle
is a violation of the Ching He way.
Fixer Celestial is in.
GERALD CHEN
You're also looking for Gerald Chen.
I was commissioned to do so.
Who's the client?
I can't reveal their identity.
But finding Gerald
is important to Ching He.
You need to know that.
This is about Ching He's survival.
Gerald has something in his possession
that we have to retrieve.
The survival of Ching He Temple
relies on a Yeh Yueh Tong fixer.
Is this for real?
The chairman didn't say a lot.
Then you'll tell Mina
Gerald's wanted by Ching He.
No, we can't talk.
All right.
Since it's commissioned,
it shouldn't be an issue.
As we're starting out,
I need a favor.
Just a little one.
-I'm not lending to you.
-It's not that.
A rare appearance
by former Interior Minister Jerome Hsueh
and his two sons.
Besides his eldest son Tristan Hsueh,
who is currently…
Uh, uh, he's your boss?
There's no need to go on about it.
My boss likes to be called Young Gold.
-Ah.
-Isn't that right?
Uh, Mr. Young Gold, hi.
Ah. With your husband
looking after things, I feel very safe.
That's right. Let's talk later.
I'm hungry. We should eat.
Yes, let's eat.
Come on. Your boss is such a big shot.
Why didn't you say so?
-What?
-I've only prepared a simple meal.
It's fine. Young Gold likes simple dishes.
It's just simple lobster and simple fish.
-Here.
-Dig in. Okay.
Try this, huh?
Mr. Young Gold,
thanks for taking on our Felix.
As you're aware,
he is returning to the workforce
after a midlife crisis.
-Finding a job's not easy.
-What midlife crisis?
It's called getting back onto the horse.
Oh, is it now?
And when did you
hand on the gambling joint?
You never told me.
Well, now you know, don't you?
Now, having a man like your husband
returning to the workforce
after a midlife crisis,
working as my bodyguard…
-I'm so lucky.
-Mm, I hope he's behaving.
So why is Dad Young Gold's bodyguard now?
Don't be fooled
by my boss's refined appearance.
These super wealthy heirs
are getting into arguments all the time.
They make enemies,
and that's when people like us,
who are smart and capable,
help them navigate the social norms.
-Oh. Yeah, it does. It does.
-That makes sense. Good.
Oh, what fell out there? I'll go check.
Hey.
To the enemies of wealthy heirs, huh?
How did the pot lid fall on its own?
-I didn't touch it.
-I didn't put it there.
She's nagging. You eat. Come on.
I only carried out the dishes. It was Dad.
-What's going on?
-Felix, the lid doesn't go here.
-You're so careless.
-You told me to put it there.
I did not.
Keep it down, will you?
-My boss will hear you.
-Oh, sorry.
We gotta keep up appearances. All right?
-I'm holding myself back.
-And you're doing really well.
AUTHENTIC TIEN-BU-LA
Okay, here's the tien-bu-la.
-With no cilantro.
-Thank you.
Wait, wait, wait.
You said Zoe and William
are the Yuan Tao bosses.
So if we get close to William, we can--
Find out how Zoe's death
is connected to Gerald.
That shouldn't be hard.
Just kidnap William
and fucking beat him until he breaks down.
That tactic might work on scum like Sheng,
but with someone this high status,
there'll be people protecting him.
We don't wanna tip him off.
So tell me, how will you make him talk?
With people like him, you need leverage.
Something that'll force him to comply.
How'd you get leverage
on someone like that?
We found out that he's swindling clients.
Huh. My wife was scammed
by one of these bogus coins.
How did you get this information?
We've been doing the legwork.
No point waiting on you.
Don't butt in. Just focus on your swing.
Anyway, what kind of legwork
did you guys do?
Fuck!
In this fucking wind, how can I play?
Hello.
Louis Hsueh?
Uh, sure. Yeah. Let's do it.
What about the brother?
Oh, okay. Bye.
Here.
Do you come here often?
Oh, yeah. My office is right there.
You mean Yuan Tao?
I said that. Yeah.
It's the first thing in your profile.
Oh, yeah, yeah, yeah.
I wanna ask.
Why would you use a dating app?
I mean, you don't need one.
You're perfect.
Get me one more,
I might tell you.
Oh, okay.
I'll go get the, uh…
I'll just get the…
Hey, excuse me. Can… can I have a, uh…
Uh… oh.
Uh, let me see. This one.
Yeah.
PLEASE SCAN YOUR FINGERPRINT
Wow, the lowly second son sought me out.
-I'm deeply flattered.
-Let's tee off, then we can talk.
Okay.
Coincidentally, I just ran into Tristan
at the chamber of commerce.
-We talked about you.
-What did my brother say?
Plug in the flash drive,
and the hacking program will install.
Then just download files remotely.
Thanks.
-Hey, wait. Are you gonna shout me a meal?
-Next time.
Yeah, right.
I'm not a tool.
Oh, really? So he felt like
you were treating him like a tool.
That's not fair.
-I know, right?
-Mm-hmm.
And I didn't want him driving me
all the time.
Mm.
I usually split all the bills with him.
Anyway, we broke up, so it's over now.
I see, I see.
Sorry. I drank too much.
-I'm going to the restroom.
-Oh, right.
Huh. Hmm.
-Did you drop that?
-Oh, what?
Oh, oh, yes.
-Wait for me.
-Okay.
You made that engineer wait there
until the place closed.
So what?
There's nothing in there
related to Gerald Chen.
Yuan Tao also looks clean.
But there's one thing that's interesting.
Yuan Tao transferred a lot of cash
a year and a half ago
to start a new concern.
Tolita.
The person in charge
is listed as this financial influencer.
Hello, everyone. I'm Dolly. Today…
We used to do this in San He, as well.
We'd use stand-ins for a setup,
so the cops never found out.
And then I discovered
Tolita had already been accused of fraud.
But it all got hosed down,
and the news was suppressed.
This, uh, this Tolita organization.
I don't think that's enough
to ruin William.
That's why we're still here.
That's why you're here.
We want you to actually achieve something.
Can you be more polite
in the presence of a woman?
This is where Do Bit comes in.
The chance to buy into
a high-yield cryptocurrency
will never be cheaper.
Why do you want to invest in crypto?
Given your family,
starting something up won't be a problem.
My brother likes governing,
but money's my thing.
You never get too much, do you?
Then we have a shared interest,
but I prefer seeing everyone make money.
Lately, I've been watching a crypto coin.
It's getting a lot of attention.
It's called Do Bit.
A YouTuber called Dolly recommended it.
You heard of it?
I've heard of it,
but that kind of obscure product,
that's not your thing.
Wow, you're so against it.
You got inside information?
Only info on Yuan Tao,
which allows 90% of my business partners
to profit through range trading.
Oh, fuck it!
This wind today. It's really weird.
Regarding the political donation scandal,
my stance is nonpartisan.
Whoever it is, there will be justice.
Then may I ask, sir, are there individuals
with ulterior motives behind the scenes?
I've already implemented
disciplinary action.
They'll be expelled.
They've always supported us.
If he finds out--
He won't find out.
If you wanna rise to the top,
you have to be ruthless.
If ever I'm for the cut,
you must do it.
Also,
I had a call.
William from Yuan Tao said
your brother reached out.
He wants to invest in crypto.
Huh. It's a small world.
Dad, what do you want?
By blood,
you're both part of the Hsueh line.
So he also needs to assist here.
He'll be able to help us.
Dad, you can trust my judgment.
By the way, at your follow-up,
what did the doctor say?
Fundraising first.
We'll talk about it later.
Your business is the top priority.
TRISTAN HSUEH
-What are you doing?
-Uh, nothing.
I'm seeing how long I can hold a gun
before my hand starts to shake.
Whose hand doesn't shake
when it's kept raised?
Yeah, you're right.
Don't tremors happen
when the hand is at rest?
The doctor says mine is a special case.
The annoying thing is,
I have no idea when it's gonna get worse.
Guns are a last resort.
It's not important that you lift a gun.
What if, down the track,
I lose control of my legs?
Hey. On the news,
your brother's political crisis
is the lead story.
I can't be worried about all that.
Uh, us fixers.
We're always helping others
solve their problems,
but our own family matters,
they're the difficult ones.
We have to talk
to this investment adviser, Hung Kuo-lung.
What's his connection to Yuan Tao?
There isn't any.
He just runs stock market scams.
We need concrete evidence of fraud,
so you're the mark.
Huh?
Can you play mah-jongg?
I'm a master at it.
Mm?
Huh? What?
Hey. They're one-year contracts,
and no refund.
I'll suggest another tomorrow.
Okay. Yeah, bye-bye.
Hey there, buddy.
If you have any sure bets, share them.
Yeah. Are you new here?
I haven't seen you before.
I deal in seafood. It's a small concern.
Oh.
So do you hedge against inflation
by investing profits?
Cash that I can see. I trust that.
Don't be like that.
Hey, youngster, don't be like him.
If in ten years your money's worth
is halved by inflation, that's your fault.
Sorry, sir, can we begin?
Oh, right, right, right. I start.
Here, Red Dragon.
A friend of mine did some investing,
and he got scammed.
He lost millions.
I wouldn't touch it. White Dragon.
Ah. White Dragon, kong.
Let me ask you.
If eating gives you the runs,
do you just stop eating?
No, you'll eat
what doesn't give you diarrhea.
The person who called you
thinks you're scamming them, don't they?
Yes.
In this world,
there are people who will get conned,
and a lot of people who con others.
Just like the three of you here.
You guys started sharing glances
quite a while back.
If you wanna be hustlers,
practice a little before you come out.
Four characters.
I know how to play this game.
Exposing you guys as hustlers here.
Oh, that's not gonna end well.
I say
we quietly finish this round,
you let me win, then we're all good.
We aren't hustlers.
We know all about you.
We need you, a hustler, to help us out.
-Help from me?
-Uh-huh.
You think you can afford it?
Mm-hmm.
Hold on.
I must be getting old. I can't beat you.
Couldn't beat me
when you were younger either.
Aren't you super busy?
You got time for this?
Since Tomb-Sweeping Day,
Dad's health got worse.
I know you don't want to see him.
You know it's not that.
He doesn't want to see me.
He heard you've started investing.
That made him happy.
Did William say that?
If you want my advice,
if you wanna invest,
there are better options.
What's wrong with William?
How do you know him?
There's nothing wrong.
I met him at a cocktail party.
I don't feel that he's honest
or even clever.
Don't rush into anything.
Come on.
-You still wanna play?
-One last game, okay?
CANNON
SOLDIER
Check.
Well, that was a risky move.
You're left with a chariot and a cannon,
yet you want to capture the general.
HORSE
CHARIOT
Well, who said I was after the general?
As all the pieces around it are taken,
the general will eventually be caught.
Did you come here
to save or sacrifice the general?
This old elephant.
He's vulnerable,
and that's all I can handle.
There was a big case recently,
and my fixers screwed it up.
It was put down to my age,
and I was accused of poor leadership.
They said I'm old, and I should step down.
If they really want you gone,
they'll find any excuse.
And I still need
an old elephant around. Hmm?
I'm afraid
that this old elephant will get taken out
before it can offer you any protection.
Madam Fan.
Keep an eye on Mina.
Find out what she's discovered lately.
Got it.
Target Zoe confirmed dead.